[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are helping
Grandpa Pig pick vegetables.
Peppa, here is a lettuce.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Oh, what's that?
Aah! There's a horrible monster
on it.
[SNORTING]
Monster.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
That's not a monster.
It's just a little snail.
PEPPA:
Oh, where has he gone?
GRANDPA PIG:
He's hiding in his shell.
PEPPA:
Is that where he lives?
GRANDPA PIG:
Yes, it's his house.
Look, he's coming out again.
Hello, Mr. Snail.
[LAUGHS]
Grandpa, does Mr. Snail
have a bed in his house?
[LAUGHS]
No, Peppa.
If I were a snail
I'd have a bed and a table
and a chair and a fridge
and a television.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Grandpa, what do snails eat?
Well, mostly they eat
my vegetables.
[MUNCHING]
GRANDPA:
Oi, stop that,
you cheeky rascal!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Grandpa, George and I
want to play cheeky snails.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
These baskets
can be your shells.
There, now you look
like two cheeky snails.
[GIGGLES]
I'm going to eat up
all Grandpa Pig's lettuce.
Oi, keep off my lovely lettuce,
you cheeky snails.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
And when Grandpa Pig
shouts at me
I'll hide
in my little house.
[GIGGLING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[BELL RINGING]
All of Peppa's friends
are here.
[BLEATING AND BARKING]
[LAUGHING]
Hello, Grandpa Pig.
Hello, Suzy.
Have you come to play
with Peppa and George?
Yes.
I don't know where they are.
[PEPPA & GEORGE GIGGLING]
It's just me
and these two snails here.
PEPPA:
We are cheeky snails
[PEPPA AND GEORGE
GIGGLING]
Surprise!
[BOTH SNORTING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
We were pretending to be snails.
[BLEATING]
Can we be snails too?
I don't think I have
enough baskets
for you all.
ALL: Aww!
You could be
something else, though.
Something exciting
from the garden.
A carrot?
Rebecca Rabbit likes carrots.
GRANDPA PIG:
No, Rebecca, not carrots.
Come over here.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[BUZZING]
[SNORTS]
What's that buzzing sound?
It's coming
from that little house.
Grandpa,
why is that doll's house
making a funny
buzzing noise?
That's not a doll's house,
Peppa.
It's a bees' house.
It's called a hive.
ALL:
Ooh.
Look, here's one now.
[SLURPING]
PEPPA:
What's he doing?
GRANDPA PIG:
She's collecting nectar
from the flower,
and then she flies back
to the hive
to make it into honey.
Hmm. I like honey.
Let's pretend to be bees.
[BUZZING]
Yes, let's be bees.
[LAUGHING]
[ALL BUZZING]
My, what busy bees.
Yes, we're busy bees.
[BUZZING]
Now we must fly back to our hive
to make honey.
[ALL BUZZING]
[ALL LAUGHING AND BUZZING]
Goodness me.
What do we have we here?
Granny, we're busy bees.
[BUZZING]
Ah, would you busy bees
like some toast?
ALL: Yes, please!
GRANNY: And what would you like
on your toast?
ALL: Honey!
That's lucky,
because that's what I've made.
Toast and honey.
ALL:
Hooray!
I like being a bee,
because they eat
lots of lovely honey.
I like being a snail,
because they eat
all Grandpa's lettuce.
[GIGGLES]
Oi!
Oh!
You cheeky rascal.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today, as a special treat.
Peppa and George are visiting
Daddy Pig's office.
Daddy, what do you do
at your office all day?
Lots of fun things.
[SNORTS]
You'll see.
This is the building
where Daddy Pig works.
We're here.
PEPPA:
Hooray!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[BUZZES]
WOMAN [ON INTERCOM]: Yes?
Hello. It's Daddy Pig.
Hello, Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
Can I press the button too?
[LAUGHS]
Of course, Peppa.
[BUZZES]
Yes?
It's me.
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
WOMAN:
Hello, Me.
Come in.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[ALL LAUGH]
My office
is on the top floor.
We have to go up
in the lift.
[SNORTS]
Can I press the button?
I think it's George's turn.
Press the top button,
George.
[LAUGHS]
BOTH:
Ooh.
NARRATOR:
The lift is taking Peppa,
George and Daddy Pig
up to the very top floor.
PEPPA AND GEORGE: Wow!
FEMALE VOICE: Top floor.
Doors opening.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
This is Daddy Pig's office.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Daddy Pig.
Mr. Rabbit and Mrs. Cat
work with Daddy Pig.
I've brought two very special
visitors with me today:
[SNORTS]
Peppa and George.
What an honor.
Let's begin the tour.
Mr. Rabbit, can we start
at your desk?
We certainly can.
[CLEARS THROAT]
My job is all about numbers.
I take very important
pieces of paper.
I take a rubber stamp
and I stamp the paper.
[THUDDING]
BOTH:
Wow!
What a great job
Mr. Rabbit has.
Can I do some stamping?
Of course.
I'll just find you some paper.
[SNORTS]
Here's some paper.
[THUDDING]
[LAUGHING]
Uh, maybe we should use
some blank paper.
Here you are.
Peppa likes stamping
with rubber stamps.
I like doing
Mr. Rabbit's job.
[THUDDING]
[GEORGE AND PEPPA LAUGHING]
On with the tour.
[SNORTS]
Next up is Mrs. Cat's desk.
[MEOWS]
Hello, Peppa and George.
[SNORTS]
Hello.
My job is all about
drawing shapes
on the computer.
[BEEPING]
PEPPA AND GEORGE:
Ooh.
Then I print the shapes out.
[WHIRRING]
PEPPA AND GEORGE:
Wow!
[LAUGHING]
And here's another copy.
[WHIRRING]
Thank you.
What a nice job
Mrs. Cat has.
Can I have a go?
Maybe it's George's turn
now.
That's right, George.
It's your turn
to do some work.
[SNORTING]
[LAUGHING]
George is making
blue triangles.
Now we print them out.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[WHIRRING]
[PEPPA AND GEORGE LAUGHING]
I like doing
Mrs. Cat's job.
[DADDY PIG LAUGHING]
Do you want
to see my desk now?
Yes, please.
[SNORTS]
This is Daddy Pig's desk.
My job is quite
complicated.
I take big numbers,
transmute them
and calculate
their load bearing tangents.
Daddy Pig's job
sounds very important.
Do you use rubber stamps?
No.
Do you use a computer?
No. But I do use
coloring pens.
Daddy, can we draw
with your coloring pens?
Good idea.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Peppa and George love drawing
with coloring pens.
I'm drawing a house.
George is drawing
a dinosaur.
[GIGGLES]
George always
draws dinosaurs.
Dinosaur.
Grrr!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[ALARM RINGING]
My goodness.
Five o'clock already.
It is home time.
I say, what a splendid picture
of a house.
And what a fierce dinosaur.
George and I
have been doing Daddy's job.
And they've been doing it
very well.
I like doing
Mr. Rabbit's job.
And I like doing
Mrs. Cat's job.
But I like doing
Daddy's job the best.
[ALL LAUGH AND SNORT]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Grandpa Pig is taking
Peppa and her friends
for a day out on his boat.
[SNORTS]
Everyone on board?
ALL:
Aye, aye, Captain Grandpa!
Full sail!
ALL:
See you later!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa and her friends
are all wearing life jackets.
[SNORTS]
George, you could wear
my pirate hat.
[SNORTING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Today, we are sailing
to Pirate Island.
ALL:
Ooh.
If we're lucky,
we might find buried treasure.
ALL:
Wow!
Pirate Island sounds like
a great place.
Land ahoy!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Here we are.
Pirate Island.
ALL:
Hooray!
What's that?
It's a metal detector.
It finds buried treasure.
ALL:
Ooh!
[BEEPING]
Grandpa Pig is using
the metal detector
to find buried treasure.
[BEEPING]
Ah-ha!
The metal detector
has found something.
Let's dig it up.
It's a little coin.
Treasure.
ALL:
Hooray!
Let's find some more.
[BEEPING]
Ah-ha!
We've found something else.
It sounds big.
[ALL LAUGHING]
My goodness.
This piece of treasure
is quite heavy.
Oh, dear.
That is not
buried treasure.
That is a rusty,
old shopping trolley.
Oh.
[ALL LAUGHING]
That's enough
treasure hunting.
Who wants to help
build a big sand castle?
ALL:
Me! Me! Me!
What a good idea,
Granny Pig.
[SNORTS]
I'll just check on the boat.
Granny Pig is going to help
the children
build a big sand castle.
And Grandpa Pig is doing
important boat things.
Ah, this is nice.
[YAWNS]
Maybe I'll just
close my eyes
for a little bit.
[SNORING AND WHISTLING]
Granny and the children
are making a big sandcastle.
They need lots
and lots of sand.
They use buckets
to make the castles turrets.
[LAUGHS]
What a splendid castle.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Time to go home.
Oh! Where's the boat gone?
PEPPA:
Look, Granny!
[SNORING]
Oh, no. Grandpa Pig
is fast asleep,
and the boat
is drifting away.
GRANNY PIG:
We have to wake Grandpa up.
Shout as loudly as you can.
ALL:
Grandpa Pig!
Wake up!
Oh, no.
Grandpa Pig is still asleep.
Grandpa's too far away
to hear us.
[SNORTS]
We're stuck on Pirate Island.
We're castaways.
[BLEATS]
We'll be here
for a hundred years.
We'll have to eat
wild fruit and berries.
[BARKS]
And well have to eat
insects and slugs.
[ALL GRUNT]
[ALL LAUGHING]
The parents are here
to collect the children.
[SNORING AND WHISTLING]
Where am I?
ALL:
Hello!
Uh, hello, everyone.
Have you had a nice time?
Yes. Uh...
Actually, I just left
something behind.
Back in a tick.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Look.
There's Grandpa.
We're saved.
ALL:
Hooray!
Welcome aboard,
me hearties.
Naughty Grandpa Pig.
We thought
you'd left us behind.
Sorry about that,
Granny Pig.
Next time I promise
not to fall asleep.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Goodbye, Pirate Island.
See you again soon.
[SNORTS]
I love Pirate Island.
Can we visit it again?
[LAUGHS]
Of course we can, Peppa.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today it is raining
a little bit.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Peppa, George,
put your rain clothes on.
When it rains, Peppa and George
must wear their rain clothes.
Yuck!
George does not like
wearing his rain hat.
George, you must
keep your hat on.
Why?
Because you must keep dry.
Because you might
catch a cold.
Why?
George, do you want to play
in the garden?
[SNORTING]
Then keep your hat on.
[SNORTS]
Come on, George!
Peppa and George are going
to jump in muddy puddles.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Yuck.
George does not want to wear
his rain hat.
[LAUGHING]
MOMMY PIG:
Peppa! George!
Come inside!
The rains too heavy
to play in now.
[SNORTS]
Oh, George.
Where's your hat?
[SNEEZES]
George has caught a cold.
Oh, poor little George.
You don't sound well.
[COUGHS]
[SNORTS]
Don't worry.
I'll ring
Dr. Brown Bear.
[DIALING]
[RINGING]
Dr. Brown Bear speaking.
I see.
Put George to bed
and I'll be straight round.
Thank you,
Dr. Brown Bear.
Goodbye.
Will George be taken
to a hospital
and given medicine?
No. George just has
to go to bed.
Oh? So George
is not really, properly ill.
[SNEEZES]
Ugh! That's disgusting!
[COUGHING]
Poor George.
Let's get you
straight to bed.
[♪♪]
George,
you have to stay in bed
for a bit.
No.
George does not want
to stay in bed.
[SNEEZES]
George, you have
to stay in bed
until you are better.
Why?
Because you have
to keep warm.
Why?
Uh...
Because Dr. Brown Bear says so.
Hello. Where's my patient?
[GASPS]
Open wide and say, "Ah."
George is a little bit
worried.
Hmm. Peppa, you're big
and brave.
Can you show George
how to say, "Ah"?
[SNORTS]
Of course.
Ah.
[GIGGLES]
Hmm. George has
caught a cold.
Does George need
medicine?
No. But he can have
some nice warm milk at bedtime,
to help him sleep.
Thank you,
Dr. Brown Bear.
You're welcome.
Goodbye.
[HORN HONKS]
George has been in bed all day.
Now it is Peppa's bedtime.
George, are you better?
[SNEEZES]
George is not better.
George, please don't sneeze
so loudly.
[COUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
This is impossible.
George, here's
some nice warm milk,
to help you sleep.
[SLURPS]
[YAWNS]
The warm milk makes George
feel very, very sleepy.
Good night,
my little piggies.
[YAWNS]
It's so nice and quiet.
[GEORGE SNORING LOUDLY]
[ROOSTER CROWING]
It is morning.
[SNORING LOUDLY]
George has slept very well.
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]
[LAUGHING]
[BED CREAKING]
[YAWNS]
[ROARS]
George is better.
[GIGGLING]
Come on, everyone.
It's a lovely, sunny day.
[SNORTS]
George is wearing
his rain hat.
He doesn't want to catch
another cold.
Oh, George.
You don't need
to wear your hat.
Why?
Because it's hot
and sunny.
Why?
George, can you stop
saying "why" all the time?
Why?
[GIGGLING]
[LAUGHS]
George certainly is better.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
[GIGGLING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND GIGGLING]